

Balázs Sárközi

Software engineer

CONTACT

Address

Vadász u. 3

Szolnok 5000

Phone Number +36705973833

Website

sarkozibalazs.dev

Email Address

hello@sarkozibalazs.dev

CERTIFICATIONS

Sap certified ABAP developer

AWS solutions architect

DevOps Deployment Automation

with Terraform

LANGUAGES

Hungarian

English

German

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web design

DHD

Node

Frontend frameworks

VueJs, React

System administration

Infrastructure management

Circuit Board design

Manufacturing

Fusion 360 cad, Grbl, Mach4

Robotics

PROFILE

I'm a software engineer, with over 5 years of experience in full time professional freelance software development. I'm mostly specialized in web based solutions, with a focus on ecommerce, erp systems, and SaaS applications. Recently took up hardware development with a focus on robotics, and home automatization

EDUCATION

Budapest University of Technology and Science

Software engineer

University of Óbuda

Electrical engineer

(September 2018 - Present)

(September 2004 - August 2011)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Telenor Hungary

Trainee

(May 2007 - August 2009)

(October 2009 - June 2010)

(May 2011 - March 2012)

Key responsibilites: maintained old services and developed new funcionalities, mostly for the Telenor mobile portal, and other Telenor platforms.

Win Trade 2000 bt.

Erp system developer

Key responsibilites: developing new features for the internal erp system

STV Services Gmbh

System administrator

Key responsibilities: maintaining IT infrastructure, providing desktop support

Viale kft

Full Stack Web developer

(September 2012 - November 2013)

(February 2014 - December 2014)

Key responsibilites: developing new ecommerce features

Aton technology ltd.

Backend engineer

Key responsibilites: maintaining and developing existing backend codebase on an SaaS system.

Freelancer

Software engineer

(July 2012 - Present)

I started working on side projects as a freelancer in 2012. Since 2015 its my main occupation.

PROJECT HIGHLIGHTS

Lisa Erp

Lisa Erp is a custom erp system. It handles the daily operations of a company employing 40+ people, including retail, ecommerce, inventory and warehouse management, finance, etc. Technologies: Php, Javascript

Abacus

Abacus is a dropship support tool, integrates 14 hungarian distributors, handling over 200.000 products real-time. The system is capable of tracking individual product stock status, price changes across every distributor and can manage connected retailer database. Abacus is managed through Terraform, can automatically deploy and scale. Technologies: Php, Laravel, Terraform

SDP - Survey Drone Project

The Survey Drone is an 550mm agricultural survey drone based on the Pix Hawk 3 flight controller. It helps monitoring crop health, including growth, pest and diseases, and drought. Currently it has over 200 hours of flight time.

REFERENCES

Becskereki Gábor

IT expert +36302768727 Becskereki.Gabor@ksh.hu

Arnold Velansits

Developer +36704099257

Tamás Wittinger

Digital Platform Manager +36306892713

kontroll@videojatekbolt.hu